<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    
    <string id="st_sid_jelly">
        <text>That's a nice little artifact you have there, stalker. Say, you want something stronger than that peashooter of yours? I have a good pre-owned shotgun here, I'll take that artifact off your hands.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_sid_jelly_done">
        <text>Nice work, stalker. Here you go. Be sure to remember your old pal Sid when you become rich, ok?</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_sid_patches">
        <text>These bandits are proving to be a scourge on my business. Usually they stay away from the Cordon but they're showing up here more, harassing rookies. Show them the door, stalker.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_sid_patches_done">
        <text>Good work, stalker. There's no shortage of the bastards running around but this will make it a lot easier for you.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_sid_salmon">
        <text>I have a great many connections and know the right strings to pull to get some good quality gear. I don't do it for just anyone, though. Bring me something good...smoked salmon...that I can enjoy on my crackers, and we will toast to our newfound partnership.</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_sid_hipower">
        <text>One of the rookies came to me asking for a basic detector. He doesn't have much cash but he did have a lot of firepower on him. He's willing to trade this handgun for a basic detector and dosimeter.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_sid_cigar">
        <text>The officer at the checkpoint has a taste for fine things. He's offered some good equipment in exchange.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_loris_ak">
        <text>Stalker, are you really running around with that pea shooter? At this rate you'll be dead so quickly there won't be anything valuable to strip off your corpse. I have this old AK, real Cold War relic, and customers aren't too keen on it because they prefer more modern, lighter weapons. I'll let you have it if you get me something decent to eat.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_loris_ak_done">
        <text>Thanks, stalker. I could really use something to wash this down, too, hmm..</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_loris_762">
        <text>Need ammo for that AK? I happen to have a few crates lying around. Get me something to drink and we'll have a deal.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_loris_762_done">
        <text>Thanks, stalker. I have to wait for Sid to get another shipment in, but keep the beer coming.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_loris_generic">
        <text>Ammo is always in pretty short supply here for the rookies to keep themselves safe. If you have any on hand, I'll be willing to trade some basic medical supplies for it.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_loris_generic_done">
        <text>Thanks, stalker. Keeping the rookies armed helps keep them alive, and profitable.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_xenotech_scrap">
        <text>As you know there's no shortage of things to fix around these parts - I have all the tools I need, but finding spare parts can be hard, especially because most of it gets glossed over. If you can find any scrap or screws, I'll be willing to trade you some of my excess repair supplies.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_xenotech_scrap_done">
        <text>Thanks for the help, stalker. This will do for now.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_xenotech_gun">
        <text>Some bandits showed up from the checkpoint last night. We drove them off thankfully, and one of them dropped their machine gun after it jammed on him. It's in pretty bad condition but it's a solid model. If you can find a few things to fix it up and it can be yours.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_xenotech_done">
        <text>Here you go. Use it well.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_xenotech_lamp">
        <text>Hi, you must be pretty new here. If you plan on doing any exploration at night, it might be a good idea to get a headlamp. I should be able to put one together for you. If you can get me some spare parts, I'll see what I can do.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_outpost_ammo">
        <text>Can I bum some smokes off you? I'll trade you some of my ammo.</text>
    </string>

</string_table>