<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>
<string_table>
    
    <string id="st_hunter_meat">
        <text>Stalker, have you had mutant meat? I know it's not that great, but I've got some contacts on the outside who will pay a pretty penny for some salted, seasoned mutant jerky. The more exotic, the better, eh? So if you bring me meat, I'll be sure to keep you supplied with the means to keep bringing in meat, if you know what I mean.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_meat_done">
        <text>Thanks, stalker. I've got enough of this type for now.</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_hunter_knife">
        <text>You don't look like you're equipped to hunt. I have a spare hunting knife - prove to me you're at least capable of killing a Flesh or something and it's yours.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_knife_done">
        <text>Not bad. Here you go.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_hunter_toz">
        <text>Are you really trying to hunt with that thing? You're going to end up wasting ammo just to bring down a pig! A hunter can't really hunt effectively without a good rifle, so, bring me the pelt of a boar and I'll give you a good rifle.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_done">
        <text>Good work. Here you go.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_mp412">
        <text>I can always use some good food to eat. I can't leave this place though, the hunters here rely on me for supplies. Are you a half decent cook? Bring me some decent food and I'll give you this hunting pistol.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_tozcer">
        <text>I have a spot missing in my trophy collection - a Chimera's hide, horns and claws. I trust if you can get it for me, I'll bequeath you my personal shotgun.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_hunter_tozcer_done">
        <text>Excellent work! Here you go, use her well.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_mutants_killed">
        <text>killed mutants:</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_flea_containers">
        <text>The diggers are having good luck finding artifacts, but not so much luck moving them around. Can you bring us some containers?</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_flea_artifacts">
        <text>Looking to swap artifacts? You came to the right place.</text>
    </string>
    
</string_table>