<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1251"?>

<string_table>
    <string id="st_pliers">
        <text>Pliers</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_pliers_desc">
        <text>Basic slip joint pliers. Finding tools that aren't rusted in the Zone is a challenge as few people think of bringing these from the outside. These are good for holding large objects in place but are very big and chunky.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_screwdriver">
        <text>Flat head screwdriver</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_screwdriver_desc">
        <text>Large flat head screwdriver. Can be used for unscrewing, prying, or as a makeshift chisel in a pinch. Very useful.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wrench">
        <text>Wrench</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wrench_desc">
        <text>Wrench likely taken from an automotive shop or something. Fits only two sizes of hex nut.</text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_pliers_n">
        <text>Needlenose pliers</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_pliers_n_desc">
        <text>Smaller set of pliers with tapered jaws. Allows for manipulation of small things and is very useful to fish things out of holes. These have a brushed finish.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_screwset">
        <text>Screwdriver set</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_screwset_desc">
        <text>Set of small and thin Phillips and flathead screwdrivers. Designed for compactness and utility over pure torque application. Not in demand for stalkers but mechanics make good use of these to maintain equipment and tinker.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wrench_ratchet">
        <text>Ratcheting wrench</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_wrench_ratchet_desc">
        <text>Ratcheting wrench with adjustable clamping head that can fit multiple sizes of nut or bolt. Less sturdy than single piece wrenches but can fit smaller bolts with less fuss. Probably the best choice to hold or turn bolts with, whatever applications of such are in the Zone.</text>
    </string>
    
    <string id="st_files">
        <text>Set of small files</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_files_desc">
        <text>Set of professionally made files with different patterns and grit. Very high quality and likely procured from a machine shop or factory. </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_screwtorque">
        <text>Torque screwdriver and bit set</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_screwtorque_desc">
        <text>Torque screwdriver with a set of screwdriver heads, including Philips, flat, hexagonal and Torx. Adjustable torque setting allows the mechanic to set the exact required tightness of a fastening. Very rare and not used much in the Zone except to maintain otherwise finicky exoskeleton frames.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_tweezers">
        <text>Set of tweezers</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_tweezers_desc">
        <text>Set of fine tweezers. Commonly used to manipulate solder or place electronic chips.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_soldering">
        <text>Portable Soldering Iron</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_soldering_desc">
        <text>Portable soldering iron with battery pack. Some ingenious soul managed to encapsulate a Flash artifact in the batteries, giving it limitless power. Said person also forgot to include a means to hold the hot iron when not in use. Be careful not to burn yourself!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_micrometer">
        <text>Micrometer</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_micrometer_desc">
        <text>Precision mechanical calliper that can take measurements as accurate as 1/100th of a millimeter. Produced in Germany. </text>
    </string>

    <string id="st_pins">
        <text>Hammer with pin punches</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_pins_desc">
        <text>Small hammer with a set of standard sized pin punches. Used for advanced disassembly of weapons and weapon components, as well as adjusting iron sights. Common with organized groups in the Zone that have the time and luxury to fine-tune their weapons.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_press">
        <text>Portable ammo press</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_press_desc">
        <text>Adjustable ammo press that fits any brass case from pistol to rifle. Just mount to a sturdy table and press your worries away!</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_powder_kit">
        <text>Powder measuring kit</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_powder_kit_desc">
        <text>Set of funnels, cups and scales used to measure and pour propellant. A must-have for any respectable hand loader.</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_trimmer">
        <text>Case trimmer and deburring tool</text>
    </string>
    <string id="st_tripper_desc">
        <text>A hand-operated brass case trimmer with an insert to deburr the case lip.</text>
    </string>
</string_table>